{
    "subject": "resource/SISTERS_Magazine",
    "predicate": "ontology/editor",
    "object": "resource/Na'ima_B._Robert",
    "human_readable": "Na'ima B. Robert is the editor of SISTERS Magazine.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.957231879234314,
            "question": "Does Na'ima B. Robert have a specific role within SISTERS Magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9505156874656677,
            "question": "What role does Na'ima B. Robert have in SISTERS Magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9220521450042725,
            "question": "Is Na'ima B. Robert involved with a magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9185751080513,
            "question": "What is the name of the magazine edited by Na'ima B. Robert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8967639803886414,
            "question": "Who is the editor of SISTERS Magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8688309788703918,
            "question": "Name the person who edits SISTERS Magazine."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8016701340675354,
            "question": "What is the name of the magazine Na'ima B. Robert works for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7969738245010376,
            "question": "Who edits SISTERS Magazine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6707800030708313,
            "question": "Is Na'ima B. Robert involved in the publishing industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6267433762550354,
            "question": "What type of publication is SISTERS Magazine?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Na'ima B. Robert is the editor of SISTERS Magazine.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5295_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Na'ima B. Robert involved in the publishing industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5295_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who edits SISTERS Magazine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5295_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the magazine Na'ima B. Robert works for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5295_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5295_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that \"Na\u2019ima B. Robert is also the founding editor of \u201cSISTERS,\u201d a magazine that caters to Muslim women.\" This supports the statement that Na'ima B. Robert is the editor of SISTERS Magazine."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}